hi-tec.com 2006-12-11

# :: Hi-Tec.com - Worldwide - Privacy Policy ::

INTRODUCTION  
The protection of your privacy is important to Hi-Tec. This statement discloses information practices of Hi-Tec, including what type of data we may collect and hold, how it is used and with whom the data is shared. It also explains how you can contact us if you have any queries or concerns about your personal information.

This Privacy Statement is applicable to data collected by Hi-Tec and other Hi-Tec associated companies in Europe that distribute Hi-Tec's products. In order to help you understand how we will use the data you provide, the following guidelines have been created.

In general, it is possible to access our sites without supplying any personal data. But in the cases where personal information is collected it is used primarily to best provide the services you might request and secondly to improve how Hi-Tec might serve you, by making appropriate use of the information. Further, we may also use this information to send you from time to time information about Hi-Tec products and services that we think may be of interest to you. Unless required to do so by law and as set out in this policy, we will not share, sell or distribute any of the information you provide to us without your consent.

DATA STORAGE AND SECURITY  
The data may be transferred, stored and processed inside or outside the European Union and anywhere in the world but will not be disclosed to anyone outside the Hi-Tec Group, its associated companies or other companies who provide services of assistance to Hi-Tec's customers. We employ security measures to protect your information from access by unauthorised persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage. We will retain your information for a reasonable period or as long as the law requires.

This information will be treated in accordance with the Directive 95/46/EC of the European Parliament in accordance with national laws passed pursuant to the Directive.

YOUR CONSENT  
By submitting your information you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page, and may place notices on other pages of the website, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. Note that continued use of the service will signify that you agree to any such changes.

COOKIES   
Hi-Tec may use 'cookies' which are small amounts of information that we store on your computer. Most internet browsers can be set to notify you when you receive a cookie (allowing you to decide whether or not to accept it) or to reject all cookies. If you elect to reject cookies from this site certain features may not be able to be used by you.

If you have not set your browser to reject them, our system will issue cookies to your computer when you visit this site. Cookies make it easier for you to use the site during future visits by, for example, reducing the amount of data to be entered if you have previously given it to us. They also allow us to monitor website use and to tailor the content of the site for you.

MINORS  
Minors should not provide personal data without parental consent.

LINKS TO OTHER SITES  
Links provided on our site can lead you to access sites outside Hi-Tec's control. Personal data provided to Hi-Tec will not be transported to other sites by clicking on the links. Such links are provided because they may be of interest to you or allow you to access complementary products or services provided by third parties. Hi-Tec is not responsible for the way these sites use personal data.

CONTACT  
You are entitled to see the information held about you and you may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. If you wish to do this, please contact us. We are entitled by law to charge a fee to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

Back
